

## **Albane MAGNIN**

#### Contact



71570 La Chapelle de Guinchay



B license | 30 years old



06 21 98 41 45



magninalb@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/albanemagnin

https://github.com/AlbaneMAGNIN

https://albane-

magnin.github.io/Portfolio/

## Language

French : native

English : CLES B2

## Expertise

ReactJS SASS
Javascript HTML5

PHP

IT tools

Linux GitHub Agile method Azur DevOps

## **Projects**

Available on my GitHub account and my portfolio.

#### **About me**

After 10 years of experience in the world of payroll, ERP and HRIS, including two years as a QA Referent for a SaaS payroll software publisher, I became fascinated by the job of an IT developer.

In 2022, I started training to become a Web and Mobile Web Developer and obtained my professional qualification in 2023.

This transition is a natural progression based on my experience, analytical skills, passion for technology and willingness to learn.

# Web developer

# **Experience**

• June 2023 - August 2023

C.D | Star Citizen Universe

### Fullstack developer - Javascript | Internships

Team of 4 fullstack developers.

Development of a website based on the Star Citizen universe, allowing access to public data from the game, management of organisations and their fleet of ships, and searching for objects with a social networking approach.

February 2023 - March 2023
 O'Clock School

### Front-end developer - ReactJS

Team of 4 developers: 3 front & 1 back.

Develop a comprehensive travel application for outdoor enthusiasts in France, with an interactive map showing places to stay and places to visit nearby.

March 2019 - October 2021

Fulll | Software editor

December 2019 - October 2021

#### Payroll QA Referent | Team of 3 QA

In charge of:

- Size workload for the team
- Manage deadlines
- Train and support payroll quality employees
- Same missions as those for the position of payroll quality controller

March 2019 - December 2019

#### Payroll QA Controller

In collaboration with lawyers, modellers and developers teams :

- Drafting, run, and validate tests to deploy in clients DB
- Drafting clients and internals documentations

#### • July 2018 - January 2019

Toupargel Groupe | Distribution group specialized in home grocery delivery

#### Payroll expert - Sage i7 & SAP

In charge of:

- Software updates, social monitoring, producing internal documents
- Manage payroll periods
- Bank transfers (wages, salary installments), statement of charges, social and accounting reporting
- November 2014 March 2018

CONSULTYS | Pharmaceutical engineering consultancy

June 2017 - March 2018

# Software migration manager and replacement of the payroll social manager - Sage X3

ii cliaige oi .

- Migration Ciel Paie to Sage X3
  - o Definition of needs, development of specifications, internal audit
  - $\hspace{0.1in} \bullet \hspace{0.1in} \textbf{Optimization of practices, establishment of internal procedures} \\$
  - Exchanges, meetings and training with the consulting firm
  - Start-up with respect to deadlines and provisional planning
- Payroll, personnel administration, social monitoring (200 employees); management 1 employee

November 2014 - June 2017

#### Payroll and personnel administration administrator

Assignements: payroll, absenteeism, personnel administration, training

#### **Formation**

• September 2022 - March 2023 O'Clock School | Professional Certificate RNCP Level 5

#### Web & mobile web developer, specializing in ReactJS

- 3 months learning : Javascript, PHP, Laravel, SQL, design pattern MVC, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap
- 1 month: specialization in ReactJS
- 1 month: development of the Day & Night application
- September 2013 September 2014 Université Claude Bernard Lyon 1 | Bachelor's degree
   Organizational management, major human relations
- September 2011 September 2013 Université Lumière Lyon 2 | University diploma Business and administration management, major human relations